[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "As his father, what do you think about the system that allowed this to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I think it's totally broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "And he was clearly, from what he told police, planning to commit an atrocity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "So we really can't get into the detail about what's going to happen in trial, because he hasn't been to trial for that yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Having to hand your son in, because you've just run out of options, what do you feel about Washington doing nothing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "It's a -- it's going to happen again.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "LOCATION": ["Aurora", "Colorado", "California"]}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What do you think it will take, Tricia, to wake people out of their slumber on this issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, if the Aurora, Colorado, shooting didn't wake people up and the shooting that happened in California, that didn't wake people up, I don't think Congress and the government -- I don't think you can wake them up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tricia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Blake"]}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBP", "NNP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "What did you feel in that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, we -- our intention was not to go have Blake arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "It is heartbreaking, but our son is alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "It is heartbreaking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "What is your advice to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Don't hide it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Blake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "He's -- you know, he's -- not out swimming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Bill, in conclusion, I mean, did you have any fixed view about gun control before all this hit your family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, you know the Second Amendment right and everybody's aware of that, but I think we need to peel the onion back a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "What did you discover in your show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "What you start to see is, these types of folks, they aren't in a database.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "I mean, how lax is it in reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "PURLOCK: I mean, in terms of somebody like that who has mental problems, it's very lax because none of that is reported.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What does it say about America's relationship with guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I mean, it's very much -- there's a part of this that is very embedded into our culture.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "What is the sensible compromise from what you went through with your show, could make a difference in reducing the gun violence toll?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "I mean, I feel like if you do universal background checks, it's a great start.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Why would any civilian really need one of those outside of hawk (ph) hunting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "It was pretty great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "There's a sense that within 20 years, it probably will be completely legal in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "WP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", ",", "WP", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "From what you've found in your show, is that a good thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I think that one of the things I was really -- what I -- what I was really intrigued by is the number of people who came in there, who for years had been strung out on countless medication.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "ORGAN: So that's a good thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "That's a great thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "NN", "NNPS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What is the negative?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I think that the negative From their standpoint, you know, a lot of folks that we spoke to who were kind of anti the campaign is they feel like that suddenly it's going to be -- it's going to be the '60s again and kids are going to be out, you know, just wanting to get high, and not going to school, and we're going to become this lazy bunch of people who just sit around and eat Twinkies all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "And is that a real risk, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I think it's -- I think the key is making sure that you try -- and again, it's like, you know, kids always had access to marijuana.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Isn't that one of the scariest images you've ever seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "That's -- the amazing thing is there's about 30,000 McDonald's all around the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Now you are the one person I really want to know, do you believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Well, he also didn't say he got his leg removed in surgery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "I mean, that just can't be right, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Yes, well, I think he's -- you know, again there's ways for you to go in there, so there's a way to go in and eat responsibly at all these restaurants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What do you make of Mayor Bloomberg in New York banning the sugary drinks over 16 ounces?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I mean, it's one of those things where part of me applauds the idea of something like that wanting to happen, but part of me hates the idea of having to ban anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mayor Bloomberg"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "But does that ever happen in reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "So if he's right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "-- improve the quality of life of people?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Do you ever sneak a little Big Mac in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Big Mac"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["March 2nd, 2003"]}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Do you have -- not have again since the movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Not since March 2nd, 2003.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Are you almost allergic to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "If I eat like a -- the last time I ate it, like when it hits my mouth, it just tastes like chemicals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What is your take on where America is right now and where is it going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I mean, I am -- I am an optimist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Having been the great manufacturer of the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, now you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Schieffer"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Where do you sit with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I saw this incredible Bob Schieffer I saw on TV last night who said something great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "But you're a whistle blower of sorts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Is that not in itself the justification?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I think it's -- I mean, I think that he -- what he did is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What should he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I think he should come back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What else can we look forward to in the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "One of my favorite episodes is all about kind of end of life issues, like what happens with the elderly, and so I move in with my 91-year-old grandmother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "How did that go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "It was great, I called her up and I said, hey, Thudie ph), you want to have a roommate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Do something horrible to you like sharks tend to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "REIS: Well, I've been around sharks for many years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "When you see the video, what are you thinking to yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "When I watch the video, it's almost a surreal moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Where are you going next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I'm not too sure about that yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Riding them around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Well, I'm not too sure about how many people have actually done it, per se.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "So, Jeff, what do you make of young Chris' shark riding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Well, good evening, guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff", "Chris"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What do you think of that, Jeff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Well, we -- when we vilify them, it makes it a lot easier to unsustainably exploit them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "If you're -- if you're in the water as he was in Texas, and you do get attacked by a shark, what is the most sensible course of action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "If you're religious, start praying to God.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130617pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Any regrets having heard what Jeff had to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Well, if a little bit of un-education with some of -- with a whale shark in general, that touching it might have absolutely harmed it, yes, I might feel regretful about it knowing that I might have injured it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff"]}}]